searcherzone.com 2009-05-03

# Shopping Portal

We at Searcherzone take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

### Privacy Policy

Searcherzone respects and protects the privacy of the individuals that use our Individually identifiable information about you is not disclosed to any third party as explained in this privacy policy ("Privacy Statement").

### What Information Do We Collect?

Searcherzone does not collect any unique information about you (such as your name, email address, etc.) except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information in the form of an email.

### Links to Other Sites

The sites displayed as search results or linked to by Searcherzone are developed by people over whom Searcherzone exercises no control. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information.

### With Whom Does Searcherzone Share Information?

Searcherzone will not share information about you with any advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties.

### Is Searcherzone Adware, Spyware or Malware?

Searcherzone does not monitor, collect data or 'spy' on its user base. Any software program that is implying or reporting that Searcherzone is 'adware', 'spyware' or 'malware' is incorrect. Searcherzone is incapable of tracking your overall web use or deciphering anything on your hard drive. Searcherzone does not display pop-ups or any type of advertising.

### How does Searcherzone make any money?

Some of the search engines listed in the Searcherzone may pay a listing fee or may share revenue from advertising within the search results (sponsored links).

### Your consent and changes to the Privacy Policy

Searcherzone may decide to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

### Questions and Suggestions

If you have questions or suggestions, please Contact Us or you can mail us at: info@searcherzone.com
